<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2023 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- One moving target tutorial -->
    <string name="item_title_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Press a moving target</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Change your event to click on a randomly moving target</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Click on the moving blue button as fast as possible</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_1">Let\'s complicate the game a little bit more. Now, the target is randomly
        moving.\n\nFirst, start the game and check if you can win by yourself.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_3">Once again, it seems impossible to win manually, so let\'s use Smart
        AutoClicker.\n\nYour scenario for the previous tutorial have been kept and load for this tutorial, but we will
        need to change a few parameters in order to win this new game.\n\nClick on the Scenario configuration icon to
        start updating your new scenario.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_4">We still want to click on the blue character, meaning that we still only
        need one Condition and one Action, so only one Event.\n\nAs the use case is pretty similar to the previous game,
        we will keep our Event and simply update it.\n\nClick on your previously created event to edit it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_5">In a first time, we will update the Condition that detect the blue
        character.\n\nClick on the Conditions field to display the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_6">As in the previous tutorial, we need to detect the blue character, but now
        it is moving.\n\nOur previous Condition is already detecting the blue character, but only at one position. So you
        don\'t need to take a new screenshot, as your previous Condition already has it, we just need to change its
        parameters.\n\nClick on your Condition to start editing it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_7">Currently, the Condition detection type is set to \"Exact\", meaning it
        will only be verified at its capture position.\n\nTo win this game, we need verify the same Condition, but on
        the whole screen.\n\nSelect the \"Whole screen\" type to detect the blue character anywhere on
        the screen.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_secondary_7">Detecting on the whole screen takes more time that the exact
        position, keep that in mind when your Scenario execution timing is important.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_8">That\'s it!\nWe only needed to change the detection type in order for
        your Condition to suits our needs.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_9">Close the Conditions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_10">Your Condition image is now updated!\n\nIn this state, the scenario will
        now execute a click every time the blue character is visible anywhere on the screen, but this click will be at
        the same position, the one selected during the previous tutorial. So, we need to update our Action.\n\n
        Click on the Actions field to display the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_11">We still want to execute a single click, but this time, we want to click
        on the Condition and not a fixed position.\n\nAs this is still one click, we still need only one Action, so
        let\'s edit your previous click.\n\nClick on your Action to start editing it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_12">Currently, the Click Action \"Click on\" is set to \"Selected position\",
        meaning you have to manually set the position to be clicked. The other choice is \"Condition\", meaning the Action will click on a
        detected Condition coordinates.\n\nThat`s exactly what we need to beat the game. Every time the blue character
        will be detected, this Action will click on it.\n\nSelect it to use it in your Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_13">Click on the Condition selector option to select which detected condition
        to click on.\nWe need to specify it because we can have multiple Conditions in our Event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_14">For our use case it is easy, we only have one condition, the blue character.\n\n
        Select it to click on this Condition when it is detected on your screen.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_15">That\'s it!\nYour Click Action is now correctly configured to beat the
        game.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_16">Close the Actions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_17">You have updated the Condition and your Action, there is nothing more to
        do.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Scenario dialog.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_18">One last save to register your new changes in the database and close the
        configuration dialogs.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_19">Your Scenario is now configured to beat this new tutorial.\n\nStart the
        detection with the floating menu play button and then, start the game.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_20">Congratulations!\n\nYou now know how to track a still or moving single
        target, but there is a lot more to learn!.</string>
</resources>
