<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2026 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="item_title_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text">Detect a text on the screen</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text">Learn how to detect a specific text on the screen and click when it appears</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text">Click on the button when it displays \"Hello\", as fast as possible</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_1">Welcome to the text condition tutorial!\n\nHere, you will
        try to beat the high score of a game with the help of Klick\'r.\n\nYou can first try it by pressing start game,
        or proceed to the Scenario configuration directly.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_2">Just like any other Screen Condition, we need to create a
        Screen Event first.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_3">Now, click on the Conditions field to open the Condition list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_4">We need to create the Condition. Click on Create.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_5">In this tutorial, we want to learn how to detect
        a text on the screen, so select Text Condition</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_6">A Text Condition is defined by the text to detect and the
        area of the screen to search it in.\n\nAs we want to click on the game button when it displays \"Hello\", type Hello
        in the text to detect field.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_secondary_6">The Alphabet field defines the writing system of
        the text to detect. \"Hello\" uses the latin alphabet, so you can keep the default value here, but don\'t forget to
        change it when detecting non-latin texts.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_7">Now, we need to tell Klick\'r where to search for the
        text.\n\nClick on the detection area selector to define it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_8">Position and resize the detection rectangle so it covers the
        game button, as that\'s where \"Hello\" will be displayed. Once the area is correct, press the validate button to save it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_secondary_8">Try to use the smaller possible box
        while keeping a margin around the text to detect.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_9">Your Condition is now configured!\n\nThere are now several
        adjustments that can be made to it, but the default settings suits our basic use case.\n\nClick on the save
        button to register it and return to the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_10">Close the Conditions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_11">With this Condition, the scenario knows when to trigger the Actions.\n\n
        You now need to define what Actions to trigger, so for this game, a click on the button.\n\nClick on the
        Actions field to display the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_12">An Action is something that is executed once the Conditions of its Event
        are fulfilled.\n\nIt can be a click, a swipe, a pause, an Intent (an interaction with another application) or a
        change in the Scenario execution, and multiple Actions can be defined for the same Event.\n\nClick on the create
        Action button to create your first Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_13">First, we need to pick a type for your Action.\n\nFor this game, we simply
        need to click on the button, so choose Click to create a new Click Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_14">A Click Action is defined by a position and a press duration.\n\nAs we
        want to click as quickly as possible, we can keep the default press duration of 1ms, which is the lowest
        possible value. So we only need to define a position.\n\nClick on the position picker button to select the Click
        Action position.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_15">You need to select the exact position to be clicked, so you need to start
        the game again to display the button, and then select its position.\n\nOnce the position is correct,
        click on the validate button to save it.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_secondary_15">You can\'t interact with the game while the position selector is
        visible, but you can use this button to show and hide it, allowing you to remove that restriction at will.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_16">The click is now correctly configured!\n\nClick on the save button to
        register it and return to the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_17">Close the Actions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_18">Your Event now has a Condition and an Action, which means it knows what
        to execute and when to execute it.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Scenario dialog.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_19">The only requirement for a Scenario is to have at least one Event.\n
        As our Event already cover how to win the game, we don\'t need anything else.\n\nClick on the save button to
        save the Scenario in database and close the configuration dialogs.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_20">As you can see, the play button is now available, meaning that your
        Scenario is valid and can be used for detection.\n\nClick on it to start the detection.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_21">It\'s playing but nothing happens?\n\nThat\'s normal, it will click only
        when the button displays \"Hello\", remember? While keeping the scenario running, press the start game button
        and just watch as Klick\'r will beat it for you!</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_text_conditions_still_text_step_22">Congratulations!\n\nYou now know how to detect a text displayed on the
        screen.\nTake a look at the other tutorials to discover more use cases.</string>
</resources>
