<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2026 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="item_title_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions">On Timer Reached</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions">Learn how to trigger an action at a given cycle.</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions">Click every second on the button for 5 seconds. Try to
        stay consistent to get a higher score!</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_1">Welcome to the Timer reached condition tutorial!
        \n\nHere, you will try to trigger an action at a given cycle. You can try to beat the game first, or skip
        directly to the scenario configuration to start automating it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_2">The Trigger Events are in a separate list from the
        Screen Events, click on Trigger Event icon to open it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_3">Now, click on create to create a new Trigger Event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_4">As you can see, the Trigger Event structure is
        roughly the same as the Screen Event. We need first to declare when we want to execute our actions. \n\nClick
        on the Trigger Conditions field to open the condition list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_5">For now, the list is empty. Click on the create
        button to create a new Trigger Condition.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_6">To beat the game, we need to click at a given time,
        so select the Timer Reached condition type.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_7">The timer reached condition is considered fulfilled
        after a given amount of time. We want to click every second, so let\'s use 1000 ms. \n\nThe tutorial will
        continue once you input 1000 in the \"After\" box.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_8">By default, Timer Reached Conditions are
        triggered only once, but here we want to click every second, not just one second after start. \n\nClick on the
        checkbox to restart the condition timer once it has been reached.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_9">Our condition is now configured to be fulfilled
        every second. Keep in mind that your other scenario elements will still need to be processed, so a scenario
        with plenty of enabled Events can delay this condition. \n\nClick on save to close the dialog and return to the
        Trigger Condition list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_10">That\'s all the conditions we need. Close the
        dialog to return to the Trigger Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_11">Now the event knows when to trigger its actions, but
        we still need to define what to trigger. Click on the Action field to display the action list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_12">When the condition is fulfilled (so, every second),
        we need to click on the game button. Simply create a new Click action and set its position on the game button.
        \n\nTutorial will proceed once you return to the event list with your created event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_13">Our Trigger Event knows when to act and what to do,
        we can now save our scenario and try to beat the game. \n\nTutorial will proceed once you save the scenario.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_timer_reached_conditions_step_14">Now restart the game, start your scenario and watch
        Klick\'r beat the game for you!</string>
</resources>