<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2026 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_button_next">Next</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_button_close">Close</string>


    <!-- Image Condition Capture slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_title">Image capture</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_desc">Tips about optimal image capture</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_1_text">When capturing for an image condition,
        you need to avoid changing parts such as the background. The capture needs to look as close as possible to what
        will be displayed when detecting.\n\nTry to always capture as close as possible to the target you want to match
        while keeping enough details for detection.\n\nNote: You can pinch to zoom to the capture and control more
        precisely the area.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_2_text">Be careful with images containing transparent
        areas. If the background behind the transparent surface changes, the detection algorithm will detect the changes
        in color or shape and will not consider it as detected. \n\nTry to avoid transparent parts in your condition
        while keeping enough static details for detection. You can also change the detection tolerance in order to
        compensate for the possible changes in small transparent areas. \n\nIf there is a text within the target you
        want to match, you might want to consider using a Text Condition, as they are less impacted by background
        change noise.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_3_text">Image detection is more accurate when applied
        to things to detect that have a lot of borders. It is also faster if the image is smaller, but it will lose
        confidence if the image is too small and lacks details. Try to keep that in mind when creating new image
        conditions.\n\nIf you are trying to detect very small things, you might want to use one or several Color Conditions
        instead, they are more reliable for such cases, and way faster.</string>


    <!-- Image Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_title">Detection area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_desc">Learn about the impact on your scenario performances</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_1_text">When creating an Image Condition, you can define
        where the detection will occur on the screen by changing the detection type.\n\nBy default, a new Image
        Condition will always detect at the same spot as the capture. This is the fastest way for detecting an image.
        \n\nIf the image you need to detect can be displayed at several places, you then need to use one of the other
        options.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_2_text">When selecting \"In area\", the area selection
        field will enable; allowing you to define a detection area.\n\nBy default, the area will be the same as the capture
        area, but you can move and expand it. The bigger the area is, the slower the detection will be, so try to only
        include the interesting parts of the screen.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_3_text">The last option, \"Whole screen\" will change the
        detection area to the whole display. \n\nThis is by far the slowest detection type and you should use it only
        as a last resort.</string>


    <!-- Text Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_title">Text detection area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_desc">Tips about optimal text detection</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_step_1_text">When detecting a text on the screen, you need to
        define a detection area that will be scanned for text during detection. \n\nWhen detecting static text, you
        want the area to be close to the text while keeping a small margin around it. The text should not touch the
        borders of the area or the detection confidence will drop significantly. \n\nNote: for very small text,
        you might need to increase the detection quality of your scenario, as higher resolution will help the detection
        of those. </string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_step_2_text">When detecting a text that can appear in multiple
        positions, use the smallest detection area possible. The bigger the detection area is, the slower the detection
        will be. \n\nIf the different positions are known and not random, it might be faster to use separate text
        conditions for each position than one with a very big area. You can test your timings using the debug report
        if you are into deep optimization of your scenario timings.</string>


</resources>