<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2023 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Two still targets press when both are visible tutorial -->
    <string name="item_title_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target">Condition visibility</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target">Use the Visibility option to click when the target is not displayed</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target">Click on the blue button only when the red button is not visible</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_1">Let\'s change the rules of the game again. The blue target has stopped moving,
        but now it should only be clicked when the red target is not visible.\n\nFirst, start the game and check if you can win
        by yourself.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_3">Once again, it seems impossible to win manually, so let\'s use Klick\'r.
        \n\nClick on the Scenario configuration button to start automating this game.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_4">We want to click at the same spot when the red target is not displayed.\n
        We need to create an Event that will handle that, click on the create Event button to continue.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_5">First, we need to add an Image Condition. Click on the Conditions field to display
        the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_6">Then, click on create a new Screen Condition.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_7">In this tutorial, we want to learn how to detect if an image is not on the screen,
        so select Image Condition</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_8">We need to take a screenshot of the red target, so start the game to make it visible.
        Once it is visible, take a screenshot of it!</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_secondary_8">Use the capture button in the floating menu to take the screenshot.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_9">Is your screenshot containing the red target? You can crop it in order to only
        get the part that is interesting for the detection, the red target.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_secondary_9">If your screenshot does not contain the red target, you can
        press this button to take a new one.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_10">Your Condition image is now recorded!\n\nAs the red target isn\'t moving, we
        can keep the default area configuration, which will verify only at the capture position.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_11">We want to verify if the target is NOT displayed, so we need to uncheck the
        \"Visible\" option. With this, the Image Condition will be fulfilled for each screen frames that does not display the red target.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_12">The Image Condition is now correctly configured.
        Click on the save button to register it and return to the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_13">Close the Conditions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_14">The condition will be fulfilled when the red target is not visible,
        now we need to define the action to trigger when this happens. Click on the Action field to display the Action list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_15">For now, we have no Action. Click on create a new Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_16">We need to click on the blue target, so select Click.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_17">The blue target is never moving, so we can simply define a static position for our Click.\n\n
        \n\nClick on the position picker to select the Click position.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_18">You need to select the exact position to be clicked, so you need to start
        the game again to display the blue character, and then select its position.\n\nOnce the position is correct, click on the validate button to save it.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_secondary_18">You can\'t interact with the game while the position selector is
        visible, but you can use this button to show and hide it, allowing you to remove that restriction at will.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_19">As we want to click as quickly as possible, we can keep the default press duration of 1ms,
        which is the lowest possible value. The click is now correctly configured!\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_20">Close the Actions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_21">Your Event now have a Condition and an Action, which means it knows what
        to execute and when to execute it.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Scenario dialog.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_22">All changes must be saved in your scenario in order to be registered.\n\nClick
        on the save button to save your changes.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_23">We are ready to win this game!\n\nClick on the start button to start the
        detection and then, start the game.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_combine_conditions_not_visible_target_step_24">Congratulations!\n\n
        You now know how to execute something when an Image is not visible on the screen!</string>
</resources>
