<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2026 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_button_next">Next</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_button_close">Close</string>


    <!-- Image Condition Capture slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_title">Image capture</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_desc">Tips about optimal image capture</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_1_text">When capturing for an image condition,
        you need to avoid changing parts such as the background. The capture needs to look as close as possible to what
        will be displayed when detecting.\n\nTry to always capture as close as possible to the target you want to match
        while keeping enough details for detection.\n\nNote: You can pinch to zoom to the capture and control more
        precisely the area.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_2_text">Be careful with images containing transparent
        areas. If the background behind the transparent surface changes, the detection algorithm will detect the changes
        in color or shape and will not consider it as detected. \n\nTry to avoid transparent parts in your condition
        while keeping enough static details for detection. You can also change the detection tolerance in order to
        compensate for the possible changes in small transparent areas. \n\nIf there is a text within the target you
        want to match, you might want to consider using a Text Condition, as they are less impacted by background
        change noise.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_capture_step_3_text">Image detection is more accurate when applied
        to things to detect that have a lot of borders. It is also faster if the image is smaller, but it will lose
        confidence if the image is too small and lacks details. Try to keep that in mind when creating new image
        conditions.\n\nIf you are trying to detect very small things, you might want to use one or several Color Conditions
        instead, they are more reliable for such cases, and way faster.</string>


    <!-- Image Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_title">Detection area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_desc">Learn about the impact on your scenario performances</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_1_text">When creating an Image Condition, you can define
        where the detection will occur on the screen by changing the detection type.\n\nBy default, a new Image
        Condition will always detect at the same spot as the capture. This is the fastest way for detecting an image.
        \n\nIf the image you need to detect can be displayed at several places, you then need to use one of the other
        options.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_2_text">When selecting \"In area\", the area selection
        field will enable; allowing you to define a detection area.\n\nBy default, the area will be the same as the capture
        area, but you can move and expand it. The bigger the area is, the slower the detection will be, so try to only
        include the interesting parts of the screen.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_image_condition_area_step_3_text">The last option, \"Whole screen\" will change the
        detection area to the whole display. \n\nThis is by far the slowest detection type and you should use it only
        as a last resort.</string>


    <!-- Text Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_title">Text detection area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_desc">Tips about optimal text detection</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_step_1_text">When detecting a text on the screen, you need to
        define a detection area that will be scanned for text during detection. \n\nWhen detecting static text, you
        want the area to be close to the text while keeping a small margin around it. The text should not touch the
        borders of the area or the detection confidence will drop significantly. \n\nNote: for very small text,
        you might need to increase the detection quality of your scenario, as higher resolution will help the detection
        of those. </string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_text_condition_area_step_2_text">When detecting a text that can appear in multiple
        positions, use the smallest detection area possible. The bigger the detection area is, the slower the detection
        will be. \n\nIf the different positions are known and not random, it might be faster to use separate text
        conditions for each position than one with a very big area. You can test your timings using the debug report
        if you are into deep optimization of your scenario timings.</string>


    <!-- Number Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_number_condition_area_title">Number detection area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_number_condition_area_desc">Tips about optimal number detection</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_number_condition_area_step_1_text">The tips here are the same as for the Text Condition:
        when detecting a number on the screen, you need to define a detection area that will be scanned for numbers
        during detection. \n\nWhen detecting a static number, you want the area to be close to the number while keeping a
        small margin around it. The number should not touch the borders of the area or the detection confidence will drop
        significantly. \n\nNote: for very small numbers, you might need to increase the detection quality of your scenario,
        as higher resolution will help the detection of those. </string>


    <!--Screen Condition type selection -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_type_title">Screen condition types</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_type_desc">Learn which one to use depending on your use case</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_type_step_1_text">Color condition is the fastest way of detecting
        with Klick\'r. It simply verifies the color of a pixel on your screen. \n\nThis condition is convenient when
        trying to detect simple UI elements such as a button color or progress bar completion, or small changes.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_type_step_2_text">Image condition is slower than a color condition,
        but it allows more flexibility for the screen content detection. Execution time is pretty low when detecting
        in a small area, but it can greatly increase when the area is bigger. \n\nThis condition is convenient when
        trying to detect clear shapes and colors, like the content of a card, or an icon.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_type_step_3_text">Text conditions and Number conditions both use
        the same detection process. \n\nText detection is the slowest detection type, but unlike the image detection, it is
        not sensitive to transparency and allows more precision in complex detection scenes. Execution time increase with
        detection area size and also depends on the alphabet selected. \n\nThis condition is convenient when
        trying to detect a text or a number independently of how it is displayed.</string>


    <!-- Number Condition Detection Area slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_threshold_title">Detection confidence</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_threshold_desc">Tips about detection confidence</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_threshold_step_1_text">Klick\'r does a lot of pre-processing before
        looking for your screen condition in order to speed up the process and reduce battery impact. This creates
        uncertainties and approximations in the results that are expressed as the confidence score. \n\nTo ensure your conditions are working
        as expected, you can test them individually by pressing the play arrow button while focusing a condition on the
        screen condition list.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_threshold_step_2_text">When testing a screen condition, the
        detection confidence score will be displayed, and you can modify the tolerated difference directly here,
        allowing you to get rid of false positive or be more flexible with allowed results.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_screen_condition_threshold_step_3_text">Detection results are also impacted by the
        detection resolution. Available in the Scenario dialog, it allows you to change how much Klick\'r downscales
        your screen content before processing it. \n\nThis can impact the confidence score of all of your screen
        conditions, with higher resolution meaning better detection, but also slower execution time.</string>


    <!-- Broadcast received slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_broadcast_received_title">On Broadcast Received</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_broadcast_received_desc">Listen to broadcasts from other apps</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_broadcast_received_step_1_text">On Android, when applications want to share their
        state with other apps, they use a Broadcast Intent. \n\nWith the \"On Broadcast Received\" condition, you can
        monitor those states and react with an action in Klick\'r. Some default values for the Android system state are
        provided, but keep in mind that broadcast conditions are more for developers, as mastering them requires Android
        development knowledge.</string>

    <!-- Counter Reached slideshow -->
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_counter_reached_title">On Counter Reached</string>
    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_counter_reached_desc">React to your scenario\'s counter values</string>

    <string name="tutorial_slideshow_counter_reached_step_1_text">Counters are variables declared in your scenario
        that can be modified, displayed or verified during its execution. \n\nWith the \"On Counter Reached\" condition,
        you can verify the current value of a counter to trigger actions. All mathematical comparison
        operators are available to customize the verification. \n\nCounters can be used in various ways and using a single
        counter-related condition or action is often not enough to use them correctly. Interactive tutorials covering the
        Counter feature are available in their dedicated section.</string>

</resources>