<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2023 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- One moving target tutorial -->
    <string name="item_title_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Press a moving target</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Learn how to create an event to click on a randomly moving target</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target">Click on the moving blue button as fast as possible</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_1">Welcome to your second tutorial!\n\nThis time, the target is randomly
        moving on the screen.\n\nFirst, start the game and check if you can win by yourself.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_3">Difficult, isn\'t it?\nLet\'s use Klick\'r to beat it!\n\n
        Click on the Scenario configuration icon to start editing your new scenario.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_4">A Scenario is the root structure of Klick\'r automation.\n\n
        It contains the general detection settings and a list of Events describing what will be executed when running
        your Scenario.\n\nClick on the create event button to create your first Event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_5">An Event describes what Actions (click, swipe…) to execute when certain
        Conditions are met.\n\nTo beat this game, we need to detect the blue character as it moves across the screen.
        \n\nClick on the Conditions field to display the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_6">An Image Condition is a part of a screenshot that will be compared to each screen
        frame of your device.\n\nTo beat the game, we want to click on the blue character when it\'s visible, so we need
        a Condition that is fulfilled when the character is shown on your device screen.\n\nClick on the create
        Condition button to create your first Condition.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_7">In this tutorial, we want to learn how to detect
        an image on the screen, so select Image Condition</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_8">The first step of a Screen Condition creation is to take a screenshot for it.\n\n
        As we want to click when the blue character is visible, the screenshot must contain it. Start the game again in
        order to display it, and then take the screenshot.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_secondary_8">Use the capture button in the floating menu to take the screenshot.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_9">Once the screenshot is taken, you can crop it in order to only get the part
        that is interesting for the detection.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_secondary_9">If your screenshot does not contains the blue character, you can
        press this button to take a new one.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_10">For this game, the interesting part is the blue character, so crop your
        screenshot to only get him.\n\nYou can pinch on the screenshot to zoom on it and get a better accuracy for the
        crop selector.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_secondary_10">Ensure the character is complete in the selector. Also try to
        crop it as close as possible to him in order to ease the image detection.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_11">Your Condition image is now captured!\n\nBy default, the detection type
        is set to \"Exact\", meaning Klick\'r will only look for it at the capture position. Since the blue character
        can appear anywhere on the game area, select \"In Area\".</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_secondary_11">The third option is \"Whole screen\". The bigger than detection
        is, the slower the detection will be. Keep that in mind when your Scenario execution timing is important.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_12">Click on the area selector to change the detection area.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_13">Resize the detection rectangle to the size of the game area, as the
        targets won\'t appear outside of it. Once the size is correct, press the validate button to save it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_14">That\'s it!\nWe only needed to define the detection area in order for
        your Condition to suit our needs.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_15">Close the Conditions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_16">Your Condition is now configured! With it, the scenario knows when the
        blue character is visible anywhere on the screen.\n\nHowever, since the character can appear anywhere, we
        cannot use a fixed click position — we need to click wherever the Condition is detected.\n\n
        Click on the Actions field to display the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_17">An Action is something that is executed once the Conditions of its Event
        are fulfilled.\n\nFor this game, we need a Click Action that clicks wherever the blue character is detected.
        \n\nClick on the create Action button to create a new Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_18">First, we need to pick a type for your Action.\n\nFor this game, we need
        to click on the blue character, so choose Click to create a new Click Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_19">A Click Action is defined by a position and a press duration.\n\nSince
        the blue character is moving, we cannot use a fixed position. Change the \"Click on\" setting to \"Condition\"
        to click wherever a detected Condition is found.\n\nSelect it to use it in your Action.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_20">Click on the Condition selector to choose which detected Condition to
        click on.\n\nWe need to specify it because an Event can have multiple Conditions.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_21">For our use case it is easy, we only have one Condition, the blue
        character.\n\nSelect it to click on this Condition when it is detected on your screen.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_22">That\'s it!\nYour Click Action is now correctly configured to beat the
        game.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Actions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_23">Close the Actions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_24">Your Event now has a Condition and an Action, which means it knows what
        to execute and when to execute it.\n\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Scenario dialog.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_25">The only requirement for a Scenario is to have at least one Event.\n
        As our Event already covers how to win the game, we don\'t need anything else.\n\nClick on the save button to
        save the Scenario in database and close the configuration dialogs.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_26">As you can see, the play button is now available, meaning that your
        Scenario is valid and can be used for detection.\n\nClick on it to start the detection, and then start the game.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_moving_target_step_27">Congratulations!\n\nYou now know how to track a moving target using the
        \"Whole screen\" detection type and the \"Click on Condition\" feature!</string>
</resources>
