<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
* Copyright (C) 2023 Kevin Buzeau
*
* This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
* the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
* (at your option) any later version.
*
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
* GNU General Public License for more details.
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
* along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Two still targets press when both are visible tutorial -->
    <string name="item_title_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target">Combine multiple conditions</string>
    <string name="item_desc_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target">Create and combine multiple conditions for your event</string>
    <string name="message_game_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target">Click on the blue button only when the red button is visible</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_1">Let\'s change the rules of the game again. The blue target has stopped moving,
        but now it should only be clicked when the red target is visible.\n\nFirst, start the game and check if you can win
        by yourself.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_3">Once again, it seems impossible to win manually, so let\'s use Smart
        AutoClicker.\n\nYour scenario for the previous tutorial have been kept and load for this tutorial, but we will
        need to change a few parameters in order to win this new game.\n\nClick on the Scenario configuration icon to
        start updating your new scenario.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_4">We still want to click on the blue target, but only when red on is visible.\n
        So we need to add a condition for this red target in our Event.\n\nClick on your previously created event to edit it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_5">We will combine several conditions, so we need to check the Condition operator
        for this event.\n\nThe Condition operator indicates how multiples conditions will be interpreted together.\n
        \'One\' means only one of the Conditions for this Event must be fulfilled in order
        to execute the Actions.\n\n\'All\' means all Conditions for this Event must be fulfilled in order to execute the Actions.
        \n\nAs we want to detect if two things are displayed together, we will use \'All\'</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_6">Now we need to update our Conditions.\n\nClick on the Conditions field to display
        the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_7">The previous Condition of detecting the blue target is still correct, but we need
        a new one for the red target.\n\nClick on the create Condition button to create a new Condition for it.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_8">Just like for the blue target, start the game in order to show the red target.
        Once it is visible, take a screenshot of it!</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_secondary_8">Use the capture button in the floating menu to take the screenshot.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_9">Is your screenshot containing the red target? You can crop it in order to only
        get the part that is interesting for the detection, the red target.</string>
    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_secondary_9">If your screenshot does not contains the red target, you can
        press this button to take a new one.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_10">Your Condition image is now recorded!\n\nAs the red target isn\'t moving, we
        can keep the default configuration.\nClick on the save button to register it and return to the Conditions list.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_11">Close the Conditions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_12">We now have two Conditions, one for each targets, and the Actions will be executed
        only if both are detected.\n\nClick on the Actions field to display the Action list for our Event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_13">The action is already set to click on the blue character, and it will only be
        executed when the blue and the red characters are visible together.\n\nThis is exactly the behaviour we need to beat the
        game, so no need to edit our click Action.\n\nClose the Actions list to return to the Event configuration.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_14">Click on the save button to save your Event.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_15">All changes must be saved in your scenario in order to be registered.\n\nClick
        on the save button to save your changes.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_16">We are ready to win this game!\n\nClick on the start button to start the
        detection and then, start the game.</string>

    <string name="message_tutorial_screen_condition_not_visible_target_step_17">Congratulations!\n\nYou now know how to combine multiple Conditions for an Event,
        but there is a lot more to learn!</string>
</resources>
